{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Gianluigi2.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "promettere",
            "failed": 13,
            "lastAsked": 1492104601.5329025,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to promise\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 16
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "provare",
            "failed": 15,
            "lastAsked": 1492104618.9880447,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to try\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 18
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to change",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492104477.3489547,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"cambiare\"?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "imparare",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1492104482.8728516,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to learn\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "intorno",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1492104563.2545242,
            "question": "Given the definition \"around\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "spiegare",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1492104612.3968549,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to explain\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "insegnare",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1492104540.9751458,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to teach\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "domani",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492104508.611889,
            "question": "Given the definition \"tomorrow\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "antipatico",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492104682.5664272,
            "question": "Given the definition \"unpleasant, nasty\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fermare",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1492104742.944818,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to stop\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la permanenza",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1492104746.8364315,
            "question": "Given the definition \"stay\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "andare in bicicletta",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492104672.450495,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to ride a bicycle\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "guidare",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492104685.7264805,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to drive\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'asilo",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492104675.1306868,
            "question": "Given the definition \"kindergarten\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to teach",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492104653.8912656,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"insegnare\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dovere",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1492104729.0407693,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to have to, must\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to have to, must",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492104750.772244,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dovere\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "povero",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492104783.0710454,
            "question": "Given the definition \"poor\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "comandare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492104792.102714,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to command, to give orders\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "work",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492104795.2709131,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la fatica\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "around",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492104780.6232803,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"intorno\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vincere",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492104789.190817,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to win\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "fanno",
                "loro fanno"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro fanno",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492104798.618826,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They do\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "convincere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492104786.663606,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to convince\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tu vuoi"
            ],
            "answer": "Tu vuoi",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492104911.763083,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You want\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tutto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492104943.0781312,
            "question": "Given the definition \"everything, all\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "chi?"
            ],
            "answer": "Chi?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492104917.8505657,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Who?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "come?"
            ],
            "answer": "Come?",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492104961.5460203,
            "question": "Given the definition \"What? What was that?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "io faccio"
            ],
            "answer": "Io faccio",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492104946.9902725,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I do\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to learn",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492104816.5302622,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"imparare\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la maestra",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492104965.1455214,
            "question": "Given the definition \"teacher\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lui/lei vuole"
            ],
            "answer": "Lui/Lei vuole",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492104971.321248,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He/She/You want\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la cosa",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492105046.6588767,
            "question": "Given the definition \"thing\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "volere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492105025.735441,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wish, want\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "arrivare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492105044.6596034,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to arrive\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "noi vogliamo"
            ],
            "answer": "Noi vogliamo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492104999.7204006,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We want\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to promise",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492105030.479237,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"promettere\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "durante",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492105034.215874,
            "question": "Given the definition \"during\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "settimana"
            ],
            "answer": "la settimana",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105017.9918811,
            "question": "Given the definition \"week\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to explain",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492105042.2351036,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"spiegare\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cambiare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492105130.9237008,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to change\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "poi",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492105127.6923985,
            "question": "Given the definition \"then\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "stay",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105049.1333003,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la permanenza\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ostinato",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492105096.1854944,
            "question": "Given the definition \"stubborn\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "during",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492105133.2923546,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"durante\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ma",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492105097.6570976,
            "question": "Given the definition \"but\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to try",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492105110.8252025,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"provare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nice, compatible",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492105144.2366478,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"simpatico\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dire",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492105186.178255,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to say, tell\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "voi fate"
            ],
            "answer": "Voi fate",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105183.8261907,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all do\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "voi volete"
            ],
            "answer": "Voi volete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105180.9548616,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all want\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "loro vogliono"
            ],
            "answer": "Loro vogliono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105152.0635006,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"They want\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "they want"
            ],
            "answer": "They want",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105148.0639746,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro vogliono\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lui/lei fa"
            ],
            "answer": "Lui/Lei fa",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105162.1756444,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"He/She/You do\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "he/she does"
            ],
            "answer": "He/She/You do",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105155.6320348,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui/Lei fa\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "leggere",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105188.2663631,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to read\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "kindergarten",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105196.8987913,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'asilo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to read",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105199.4783216,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"leggere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to go",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105215.6540184,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"andare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "but",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105189.7616012,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ma\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "they do"
            ],
            "answer": "They do",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105204.87823,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Loro fanno\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "y'all do"
            ],
            "answer": "Y'all do",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105202.3982599,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Voi fate\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you do"
            ],
            "answer": "You do",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105193.2825768,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu fai\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to command"
            ],
            "answer": "to command, to give orders",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105237.5765529,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"comandare\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "the week"
            ],
            "answer": "week",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105265.0041237,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la settimana\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "I want",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105240.9533248,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io voglio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "noi facciamo"
            ],
            "answer": "Noi facciamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105251.5844007,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We do\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to stop",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105272.7480447,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fermare\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Who",
                "who?"
            ],
            "answer": "Who?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105270.25222,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Chi?\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "all"
            ],
            "answer": "everything, all",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105261.979946,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"tutto\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "he/she wants"
            ],
            "answer": "He/She/You want",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105275.7640579,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lui/Lei vuole\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "teacher",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105247.4561965,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la maestra\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Perche?"
            ],
            "answer": "Perche'?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492105318.9856787,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Why?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tu fai"
            ],
            "answer": "Tu fai",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105304.8968692,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You do\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "then",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105277.6557813,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"poi\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "thing",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105287.6714823,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la cosa\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tomorrow",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105296.0882828,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"domani\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "What?",
                "what?"
            ],
            "answer": "What? What was that?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105281.96795,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Come?\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "white",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105284.9195025,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"bianco\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "unpleasant",
                "not pleasant"
            ],
            "answer": "unpleasant, nasty",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105310.6157358,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"antipatico\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bianco",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105343.8117518,
            "question": "Given the definition \"white\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sempre",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105350.0677278,
            "question": "Given the definition \"always\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la fatica",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105352.3654737,
            "question": "Given the definition \"work\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to ride a bike"
            ],
            "answer": "to ride a bicycle",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105341.5047665,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"andare in bicicletta\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "stubborn",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105324.4920855,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ostinato\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to drive",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105321.5974648,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"guidare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to want"
            ],
            "answer": "to wish, want",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105347.5838468,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"volere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "andare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105345.5501654,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to convince",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105388.7934012,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"convincere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "always",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105354.4244335,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sempre\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "poor",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105374.804291,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"povero\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to win",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105385.6932766,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"vincere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "io voglio"
            ],
            "answer": "Io voglio",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105397.451879,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"I want\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "you want"
            ],
            "answer": "You want",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105382.8017967,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu vuoi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to write",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105371.9378548,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"scrivere\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "simpatico",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105369.2620652,
            "question": "Given the definition \"nice, compatible\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "we do"
            ],
            "answer": "We do",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105399.9668038,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi facciamo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to arrive",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105420.7317934,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"arrivare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "we want"
            ],
            "answer": "We want",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105423.5108044,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Noi vogliamo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "I do",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105418.3446796,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io faccio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to tell"
            ],
            "answer": "to say, tell",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105413.5551102,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dire\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "y'all want"
            ],
            "answer": "Y'all want",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492105426.2502518,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Voi volete\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "why?"
            ],
            "answer": "Why?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105416.4944348,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Perche'?\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scrivere",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492105411.1684473,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to write\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}